<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Coherence apps]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.emergencydr.org/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.emergencydr.org/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-17T19:31:23-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.emergencydr.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dr. Bill Gray, Coherence Apps LLC]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ebola]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.emergencydr.org/blog/2014/08/17/ebola/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-17T15:42:28-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.emergencydr.org/blog/2014/08/17/ebola</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Description</h2>

<p>Ebola is a life-threatening Viral infection that comes on very suddenly, rapidly progresses to severe toxicity due to dehydration from extravasation of fluids out of circulation. Suffering is sudden and acute; fortunately, survivors cannot remember the ordeal.</p>

<p><img src="http://www.emergencydr.org/images/ebola-graphic1.png"></img></p>

<h3>How it is spread</h3>

<p>Ebola is spread by contact with bodily fluids such as blood, vomit, diarrhea, saliva. It also seems to be transmitted by eating animals which carry the virus as a reservoir; fruit bats are implicated in the current West Africa epidemic of 2014, although monkeys, gorillas, and some other animals can be carriers. Objects coming in contact with such fluids such as utensils, cooking materials, cups, glasses, needles, etc. can carry the virus from an infected person. This is why health workers wear garments to ward off any splattering, and gloves to create a barrier for physical contact.</p>

<h3>Treatment</h3>

<p>There is no proven medical treatment. No antivirals are effective against Ebola. Experimental treatments are aimed at enhancing the immune system. The bodys own immune system is capable of combating the virus, so immune serum from survivors can be used to treat people who are still sick. Monoclonal antibodies are being considered on the same theory. Unfortunately, such treatments are in extremely rare supply.</p>

<p>Supportive treatment is most important and indeed saves lives. Since dehydration is central to Ebola toxicity, providing adequate fluids is frontline in management. When possible, intravenous fluids enhance body function to the point of saving lives.</p>

<p><strong>Bedrest is absolutely necessary. Indeed, Ebola sufferers are so wiped out that they can barely even sit up in bed. Isolation and quarantine are crucial, not only for personal care, bu to prevent spread to family members and community.</strong></p>

<h2>Digitized eRemedy Support</h2>

<p>There are a few homeopathic remedies capable of stimulating the body to enhance its own functioning on every level - immune system, circulatory system, energy, organ function, psyche.</p>

<p>If used properly, these eRemedies are nontoxic and may rapidly enhance recovery through improved functioning.</p>

<p>eRemedies are MP3 files that play for only 10 sec at a time. Download speed depends on internet speed, so please be patient. Once the file is downloaded, simply click on the Start/Play button.</p>

<p><strong>You will hear just white noise as the homeopathic remedy energy is played in order to stimulate the body to heal itself.</strong></p>

<p><strong>Make sure sound on your device or computer is turned on!</strong></p>

<h3>Ebola eRemedy #1</h3>

<p><strong><em>Note:</em>To be played if:</strong></p>

<ol>
<li>Used as a preventive</li>
<li>Exposed to Ebola but not sick</li>
<li>Sick for less than 48 hrs</li>
</ol>


<p>You can either play directly from the site from here:</p>

<p><audio controls>
  <source src="http://www.emergencydr.org/assets/ebola1-83916726bae9e81e17a9955da923ca66-10s.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
  Your browser does not support the MP3 format. Use the direct link below to download the MP3 to your phone.
</audio></p>

<p>Or download <a href="http://www.emergencydr.org/assets/ebola1-83916726bae9e81e17a9955da923ca66-10s.mp3">Ebola Remedy #1</a> to your phone/mobile device.</p>

<h4>Instructions for Ebola eRemedy #1</h4>

<p>If used as a preventive, or if exposed but not sick <strong>Play once a day for 3 days</strong>.</p>

<p>If sick for less than 48 hrs:
1. Play every 15 min for 4 times
2. Then Play once an hour for 6 times</p>

<p><strong>In any case, do not play for more than 15 doses. Too many doses may stimulate the body too much.</strong></p>

<p>After following instructions, please help others by sharing your response to the eRemedy and other supportive measures whether no effect, or beneficial help by emailing a short note to <a href="&#x6d;&#x61;&#105;&#x6c;&#x74;&#111;&#x3a;&#x72;&#x65;&#x73;&#112;&#x6f;&#x6e;&#115;&#101;&#x40;&#101;&#x6d;&#x65;&#x72;&#103;&#101;&#x6e;&#99;&#121;&#100;&#x72;&#x2e;&#x6f;&#114;&#x67;">&#114;&#x65;&#x73;&#x70;&#x6f;&#110;&#x73;&#101;&#x40;&#101;&#x6d;&#101;&#x72;&#x67;&#x65;&#110;&#x63;&#121;&#100;&#114;&#46;&#111;&#114;&#x67;</a> or simply commenting on this page.</p>

<h3>Ebola eRemedy #2</h3>

<p><strong><em>Note</em>: To be played if sick for over 48 hrs</strong></p>

<p>You can either play directly from the site from here:</p>

<p><audio controls>
  <source src="http://www.emergencydr.org/assets/ebola2-e21e6970864cec4c4f68e137097ce845-10s.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
  Your browser does not support the MP3 format. Use the direct link below to download the MP3 to your phone.
</audio></p>

<p>Or download <a href="http://www.emergencydr.org/assets/ebola2-e21e6970864cec4c4f68e137097ce845-10s.mp3">Ebola Remedy #2</a> to your phone/mobile device.</p>

<h4>Instructions for Ebola eRemedy #2</h4>

<p><strong>Play 3 times a day for 3 days</strong></p>

<p><strong>In any case, do not play for more than 15 doses. Too many doses may stimulate the body too much.</strong></p>

<p>After following instructions, please help others by sharing your response to the eRemedy and other supportive measures whether no effect, or beneficial help  by emailing a short note to <a href="&#x6d;&#97;&#105;&#108;&#x74;&#111;&#x3a;&#114;&#x65;&#x73;&#x70;&#111;&#x6e;&#115;&#x65;&#64;&#101;&#109;&#x65;&#x72;&#x67;&#101;&#110;&#99;&#121;&#100;&#x72;&#x2e;&#111;&#x72;&#103;">&#x72;&#x65;&#115;&#112;&#x6f;&#110;&#x73;&#x65;&#x40;&#101;&#109;&#101;&#x72;&#x67;&#x65;&#110;&#x63;&#x79;&#x64;&#x72;&#46;&#x6f;&#x72;&#103;</a> or simply commenting on this page.</p>

<h2>Further instructions</h2>

<p>Do not use eRemedies in absence of other supportive measures. Most importantly, if there are symptoms, see a doctor or health care worker! It is important to get enough fluids orally, but intravenous fluids are also necessary. Bedrest is necessary. Hygiene must be maintained regarding vomiting and diarrhea.</p>

<p><strong>eRemedies are not treatment to be used as a substitute for full supportive care! It is merely one of several natural supportive things that can be done to enhance the bodys healing powers.</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
